<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Hector' log - Projects</title><link href="/hectormorago/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/hectormorago/feeds/projects.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/hectormorago/</id><updated>2020-04-06T20:31:00+02:00</updated><subtitle>A personal blog.</subtitle><entry><title>Projects</title><link href="/hectormorago/projects.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-04-06T20:31:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-06T20:31:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Hector Perez-Morago</name></author><id>tag:None,2020-04-06:/hectormorago/projects.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This section provides a summarize of my main projects.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Efficient Identification of Core and Dead Features in Variability Models&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Context&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Variability models play a key role in product line engineering as they 
are used to represent the common and variable features that products may 
include, and what constraints among the features must be satisfied to 
guarantee the validity of the products. Valuable analysis operations on 
variability models can be performed by black box reusing logic engines, 
such as SAT-solvers and binary decision diagram libraries. Unfortunately, 
such kind of reuse implies long computation times for operations that 
need calling the engines many times. To overcome this problem, we work 
on new algorithms that directly deal with the data structure of a binary 
decision diagram encoding a variability model. In particular, the 
algorithm published in this site is specifically designed to detect core 
and dead features&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Description&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This repository provides an algorithm to identify core and dead features, 
which is written in the C++ programming language as an extension of the 
&lt;a href="http://buddy.sourceforge.net/manual/main.html"&gt;BuDDy BDD package&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;More information about this project could be found in its&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hperez30.github.io/CoreAndDeadFeatures/"&gt;main project page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Projects"></category><category term="research"></category><category term="projects"></category><category term="others"></category></entry></feed>